ZHYAR ALI MAHMOOD

Senior Front End Developer

SUMMARY

Senior front-end developer with 3+ years of experience designing and building responsive web design and mobile apps in the financial industry. Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks, with extensive knowledge of UX and user psychology. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 80% with improved code and design.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer 2020

Iraq Surveying Iraq

Iraq surveying company was established in 2020 and the aim of the company is to provide the best engineering and surface engineering device in general for engineers and companies in Switzerland, Britain, Japan, China, Turkey, Iran

Front End Developer - Remote

2021 - Ongoing

Choveen

- Worked with team of 3 members and provided end-to-end solutions
- · Optimize application for maximum speed and scalability

Senior Front End Developer - Remote

2020 - 2021

Vootech Ottawa, Canada

Vootech was founded by a group of highly skilled entrepreneurs and IT experts

- · create an on-line store website using the Vue is framework
- · Managing software workflow.

Front End Developer

2021

KurdMad As Sulaymānīyah, Ira

KurdMad is a website largest free movie and tv streaming service with kurdish subtitle

Front End Developer

2020 - 2021

boewa.org

As Sulaymānīyah, Iraq

Boewa is a website that was created for those who want to learn and be the best in what he/she is doing, and it is the first online course website in the region , and it have been created by three youth in iraq , Sulaymaniah in 2019

· Determining the structure and design of web pages.

Senior Frontend Developer

2022

SanStore

As Sulaymānīyah, Iraq

SanStore is an online store website



EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Information Technology (IT) at Sulaimani Polytechnic University 2018 - 2022

LANGUAGES

Kurdish Native ••••

English Advanced ••••

Arabic Intermediate •••••

SKILLS

HTML · CSS · JavaScript ·

UI/UX Design · Vue js · React js ·

SEO · Vuex · Redux · MUI ·

REST FULL API · Laravel · PHP ·

Adobe Photoshop · Adobe Illustrator ·

Bootstrap · Tailwind ·

Package Manager · Node Js · Nuxt js ·

Next js · Firebase · Git & Github ·

Flutter